I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
"C-Major Pentatonic Scale"
It's no good. I can't learn this.
It's too hard for me.
Fool!
But it's better to learn the scale early.
You stupid bird! I'll show you!
Don't rush it, Koyuki-kun.
It's only been two months
since you started playing the guitar.
But he already knows the scale...
C'mon, we need a change of pace.
Let's go swimming!
Huh?!
"Lucille"
-Okay, here goes!
-Watch the ball!
What?
Umm...So please buy your own melon roll.
It's the truth. I was called
to the faculty office.
S-see you...
Hold it, Tanaka!
Yukio Tanaka of Grade 8B.
Please go to the
faculty office immediately. I repeat...
Listen, Tanaka-kun...
I don't think you're taking your job
as umbrella monitor seriously.
Huh? Oh, no...
Daily life is a series
of little jobs like this.
Maybe I should put this
in your student report...
I'm disappointed in you, Tanaka-kun.
You may go.
Wait, Tanaka-kun!
What is this?!
What happened?!
Oh...It's nothing.
We were kidding around
and Tanabe-kun did a drop kick on me.
Tanaka-kun...
And naturally, I gave it
back to him with a heel hold!
So it's no big deal!
Tanaka-kun...
-Did you catch that game?
-Yeah! That was awesome!
You look glum, Koyuki!
Maho!
Yo!
Maho, you sure eat a lot.
Huh?
Shut up. I'm hungry.
You'll gain weight.
You can have my fries.
Beck's first live performance has been set!
Huh?! R-really?
How long is this going to continue?
I'll talk to him for you.
Okay...
Okay, I'm going on deliveries,
so make up for being late
and work extra hard.
I'm sorry!
And don't forget to feed Page.
I'm off!
-He sure is strict.
-Yeah. Around strangers.
It's okay, I'll feed him.
-He's...
-You little-!
T-this is the last of it!
Oww...
Huh?! What is this?!
These aren't company documents!
They're Saito-san's personal treasure!
Treasure?
I mean, private collection.
Collection?
Koyuki, how long have you
been working here?
-Since the end of summer break.
-What for?
I want to repair the guitar
Ryusuke-kun gave me.
I didn't know...
That's why I don't want to see Ryusuke-kun
until the guitar is fixed.
Right. I understand.
So, how much do you get paid?
Oh, umm...430 yen an hour.
Are you serious?! That's crazy!
This new law sure is bad
for the manufacturing industry.
-Saito-sama, this way please.
-Yes.
Thank you for waiting.
Rie-chan! Thank you for calling her.
-Oh, it's Ken-ken!
-Rie-rie!
-I missed you sooo much!
-Me too!
What's with the get-up?
Caught a cold or something?
I'm in disguise! But how'd
you guess it was me?
You stand out too much.
Okay, it's starting!
Ryusuke-kun's guitar...
Are those bullet marks?!
Yup. They're real.
Is that...
That guitar has a name...
It's Lucille.
-Sounds like a woman's name.
-Yeah...
It's a guitar with a past...
Ryusuke got it in some dangerous place.
But...It couldn't possibly have
happened while he was performing?!
One, two!
Typhoon 24! 24-7! 24 hours straight!
BECK! B-E-C-K!
We're gonna rush at you!
We're gonna send you flyin' head-first!
Lift up your heavy ass, now
If you take off that stiff head
you'll feel totally loose
This crazy, crazy world
You just have to Stage Dive or Die
Mind blower, a shower of sweat
Run towards a new world, my life
Those who seek it will be rewarded
Pass the hot shot,
keep on coming, come on!
Blow your mind
Squeeze your sweat yeah
Squeeze your sweat
This...is Beck...
Koyuki-kun...
Can you go over to Hayakama Instruments?
Huh?! There's still more?!
-The guitar's fixed now.
-Huh?!
The one with the broken neck.
I sent it out for repairs.
I-is that true?!
You want to patch things up
with Ryusuke, don't you?
Saito-san!
Now go, hurry!
Okay!
Koyuki-kun...Deduction for leaving early.
I think this'll do.
If you notice something
while playing it, just let me know.
Now I can see Ryusuke-kun!
Hey, Tanaka...
Hey, Tanaka. Lemme play that guitar.
Yuck! What an awful sound...
suits you perfectly!
Hey, Masaru. Lemme try.
What? Forget it, Rikiya-kun.
The sound is the pits.
You laughed just now, didn't you?
-Huh?!
-Don't act innocent!
No, I thought that tune
was "Anarchy in Heaven"...
Recently, the Sex Handles-
Damn thing!
Any complaints?
Didn't think so. It was a
piece of junk anyway. Let's go, Masaru!
Yeah.
-Let's go grind someplace.
-How about New Burger?
Oh! Did you get it, Koyuki-kun?
Yeah...
Oh, good!
It's all fixed, then?
Actually, it's been slow
here at Saito Paper Company,
so getting the money
to fix it was a bit hard.
But it was worth it
to see you smiling again!
Saito-san...Thank you!
Oh, you're welcome!
Mom used to say, "From that day on,
Yukio was like someone
possessed by the guitar,
and played it every single day."
You were great at the concert!
Think so?!
I just looove your vocals, Chiba-kun!
We won't miss your next live performance!
Then I'll put you on the guest list!
Give me your names and numbers!
Hey, Ray! I've gotta talk to you!
Huh? What?
What're you mad about all of a sudden?
Wow! Ryusuke-kun, you speak English!
That's so cool!
Yeah. I lived in New York for a long time.
So I'm more used to English than Japanese.
-That's so cool!
We've got to go to New York, too!
-Tell us where you used to live!
-Yeah! We wanna visit it!
-Sure.
-Yay!
Those idiots!
I was looking for the ab machine
I bought by mail order last night...
and I finally found it!
Found what?
Look!
This is it...The L48 Eddie gave to you!
Huh? Then the one I gave to Koyuki was...
That was a fake one you got
at the guitar shop in Queens!
Which means...
-Ryusuke-kun!
Don't get tetanus!
Yukio! Telephone!
Yukio! Yukio!
I called Ryusuke too.
You're joking, right?
Oh, speak of the devil.
Sorry!
Maho...Did you really explain it to him?
I did!
Idiot! Why am I running away?!
Oh, Koyuki!
Izumi-chan!
I spoke to Ryusuke-kun on the phone
yesterday and he said to say hi.
Oh...Can you say hello from me, too?
All 9th graders will report
to the gym for curriculum guidance.
I repeat...
-It's almost graduation.
-Yeah...
I'll be lonely.
Really?
See you, Koyuki!
"Dear Koyuki-kun,"
"I've decided to stay here a bit longer,
so please take care of Page!"
He's extending his stay again!
Southeast Asia must have
something that lures grown men...
Fool!
I haven't played yet!
Punk rockers hold their guitars low...
Awright!
Yay!
Cripes! I'd better go to sleep!
"Kugatsu no Umi wa Darui Hito"
Look...
Eiji...
Look at him...
Didn't he make his band successful
all by himself?
We just do things our way.
Umm...Ginger ale.
Okay.
Hey, Koyuki! Why'd you
run away the other day?!
Sorry!
Koyuki! Let's go up front!
Let's go concrete hell,
human safari park escape
Ape in the brain,
mass brain-washing operation,
no thank you
Let's walk together, step in step,
and we'll get stuck in the deep
-I-is this what rap is?
-Let's walk together, step in step,
and we'll get stuck in the deep
-I-is this what rap is?
-We're at the rebellious age,
free as we go
-Huh? You say something?
-We're at the rebellious age,
free as we go
This is no barrier, just what is important,
nothing impure, just clear
No pressure at our pace
Who? Who? Foojin
Takes me cruisin'
Music that cuts through the wind,
free form
Bullet holes in the body...
That's a creepy guitar...
The acoustic pick-up
in the front is broken.
He has a Roger Mayer at his feet.
But...How is he getting such a sound?
Wow! Amazing!
-Hey, look at that poster!
-I'm gonna get a shot of it!
So this is where Ryusuke-kun
grew up! Isn't it cool!
Totally!
Huh?
That dog...
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Cuttlefish...
Grilled matsutake mushrooms...
"Next Episode"
"Broadcast in the School"
Grilled matsutake mushrooms...
"Next Episode"
"Broadcast in the School"
Mackerel...Eggplant, shortcake...
"Next Episode"
"Broadcast in the School"
Eat it all!